

Mohammad Reza Mohseni

Full stack web developer - (With an emphasis on Front-end technology)

Software engineer and front-end web developer with two years of experience as IT technician. I believe in excellence and have always dedicated myself, my talents and my creative abilities to assure the successful accomplishment of my goals.

mohseni.mr93@gmail.com

Rødovre 2610, Copenhagen , Denmark

@mohseni mr93

60906041

n linkedin.com/in/mo3ni

github.com/mo3ni

EDUCATION

MSC (Computer Science) - Candidate DTU- Denmark Technical University

09/2019 – Present

This study line aims to give the skills required to develop high-quality software products. It teaches well-founded methods, techniques, and tools for the modeling, construction, analysis and verification of software systems.

Full- stack web developing school HYF (Hack your future)

04/2019 – 01/2020 Copenhagen

A 6-month program for learning MERN stack (JavaScript, HTML, Css, Sxpress, Mysql React, NodeJS) , Git version control and coding collaboration

BSCS (Information technology) - bachelor KU- Kateb University

03/2014 – 12/2016 Kabul-AFG

This study line aims on theoretical and practical foundation and techniques of computation.

ICT(Information & communication Technology) - Diploma

ATVI (Afghanistan Technilca & vocational institute)

01/2012 – 01/2014 Kabul-AF

This Study line aims to give the skills of understanding IT related programs and basic programming concepts.

WORK EXPERIENCE

APT volunteer

Afghan progressive thinking

10/2015 - 02/2018

Kabul

10/2013 - 02/201

 APT was founded in 2010 by a young college graduate who had the vision of a peaceful, tolerant, open and progressive Afghan society, a vision which is shared by hundreds of thousands of other Afghan youths.

IT Technician

Gateway ICT solution company

11/2012 - 10/2014

Kabul

Responsibilities

- Assembling, reassembling the H.W devices & S.W applications
- Maintaining software, reporting and software configurations

Others (Part time)

(Net cafe owner, Computer instructor, sales assistant)

01/2011 – 06/2018 Kabul

SOFTWARE SKILLS

HTML Css JavaScript(ES6) NodeJs React

REST API Mysql Flutter (Dart) UML Git

API documentation (Swagger) Storybook Json

PROJECTS & PERSONAL COURSES

Anotate the web (11/2019 – 01/2020)

- A collaboration with Code Art company to replicate the website (https://www.annotatetheweb.com)
- GitHub source code URL: (https://github.com/HackYourFuture-CPH/FP-annotatetheweb-class10)

Job-Bazzar (09/2019 - 12/2019)

- A mobile app for young people looking to earn pocket-money in their spare time (Flutter, startup, Android, IOS)
- to create a successful software-related startup through the utilization of well-known frameworks, processes, and tools.
- GitHub source code URL: (https://github.com/Hudhud/Job_Bazaar)

Working on personal website and web projects (01/2016 – Present)

- in my home land country and in a transitional period move from AFG to Denmark, meanwhile learning programming independently
- Inspirations: (Code academy, Free code camp, Udemy, Khan academy)

TOOLS

Development tools (Good command of usage)

Visual studio code, Postman, GitHub, GitLab, Git Bash, NPM Packages, firebase, Android studio, ...

Productivity tools (Good Commnad of usage)

Slack, Adobe XD, Figma, Ms office, Photoshop, trello, Latex, Piazza

LANGUAGES

Persian

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Dari

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Danish - Took intensive course (M 3.4)

Limited Working Proficiency

Pashto

Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Attending tech conferences

Sports (mostly play football)

Chatting friends

Watching tech movies